▍2026 WTA500 新加坡站 1/4决赛
赫瓦林斯卡 6-2 6-2 梅尔滕斯 · 赛后场上采访
A big congratulations to you.
恭喜你
You've just taken out
你刚刚淘汰了
the defending champion here in Singapore.
新加坡站的卫冕冠军
Let's talk about your performance today.
聊聊你今天的表现
6-2, 6-2.
6比2 6比2
What were you most happy with?
你最满意的是什么？
Yeah.
嗯
Elise is such a solid player.
梅尔滕斯是个非常扎实的球员
She's definitely a great player.
她绝对是个很出色的球员
Tough to beat.
很难击败
So I knew that I need to play my best tennis
所以我知道得打出最好的网球
to win today.
才能赢下今天
Yeah, I just really wanted to fight
是的 我就是想拼
for every single ball, you know,
你知道 每一分都要去拼
focus on my goals for the match
专注在这场球的目标上
and give myself the best chance to win.
给自己最大的赢球机会
And yeah, I'm happy that I did that.
我很高兴我做到了
Now, I'd like to ask you
我想问问你
about how you feel overall
整体感觉怎么样
because you've played three matches here.
你在这里打了三场
You've only lost 11 games in total.
一共只丢了11局
What do you feel is clicking
你觉得是什么开窍了
while you're in Singapore?
让你在新加坡这么顺？
Um,
嗯
what's working for you?
是什么在起作用？
Well, I need to only play in Singapore,
那看来我只能在新加坡打球了
I guess.
我猜
Yes.
没错
I mean, you know, like season
我是说 你知道 一个赛季
has so many weeks and it's impossible
有那么多周 根本不可能
to just play great every single week.
每一周都打得很好
So, it's just about consistency and work
所以关键就是稳定和努力
and you got to be patient also.
还有你也得有耐心
You're going
你会
to have like tougher weeks ahead of you
遇到更难熬的几周
for sure.
这是肯定的
But yeah, I'm just happy that, you know,
但我很高兴 你知道
I stayed quite patient.
我一直很有耐心
Yeah, I worked hard and happy
我努力了
that it's paying off now.
很高兴现在有了回报
We would love for you to play
我们很希望你
in Singapore all the time,
一直在新加坡打球
but you are through to the semifinals.
不过你已经打进半决赛了
Good, Joe.
好啊
Thank you.
谢谢
You are through to the semi-finals here
你打进了半决赛
in Singapore.
在新加坡
It's your second tour-level semifinal.
你第二次打进巡回赛半决赛
How important is this for you?
这对你有多重要？
Yeah, it is for sure.
是的 当然重要
I had some tough weeks.
我经历过一些难熬的几周
So this one tastes pretty good,
所以这一场的滋味相当好
I must admit.
我得承认
All right. And lastly, lastly,
好 最后 最后一个问题
a very loud crowd once again here
今天的观众又特别热情
on this Friday afternoon.
在这个周五的下午
A lot of Polish supporters.
很多波兰球迷
Perhaps you might want to say something
也许你想对他们
to them.
说几句
Yeah, of course.
好的 当然
Yeah. Thank you guys all for coming.
谢谢大家来看球
I hope to see you tomorrow as well.
希望明天也能见到你们
Drink for me, of course.
当然 替我喝一杯
Yeah, so happy to see Polish flags
又看到波兰国旗 真开心
as well again.
又一次
You guys don't disappoint.
你们从不让人失望
So yeah, very happy and grateful
我非常开心 也很感激
for you guys and see you tomorrow.
感谢你们 明天见
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们先生们
let's hear it for Maja Chwalinska.
让我们为赫瓦林斯卡鼓掌